What's going on, at this hour?
O que está havendo?
I-I'm sorry... We just couldn't fall asleep.
Desculpe. Não conseguimos dormir.
Looks like you haven't found the guards yet.
Vejo que ainda não encontraram os guardas.
We were looking all day today, but...
Procuramos o dia todo, mas...
...I wonder if the captain learned anything?
Será que o capitão descobriu alguma coisa?
Hey, guys...
Pessoal...
The captain is okay, right?
O capitão está bem, não está?
Dammit, that was supposed to be fatal; how did you avoid it?
Droga! Era para ser um golpe fatal. Como não morreu?
Daisuke, what are you...?!
Daisuke, o que está...
Blitz Hammer!
Martelo Veloz!
They knew of our intentions.
Eles sabiam das nossas intenções.
Blow away, Wind Wall!
Sopre, Muralha de Vento!
And you call yourself vice-captain?
E ainda se diz vice-capitão?
Take a nap!
Vá dormir!
Dammit. All that effort to get the vice-captain for nothing.
Droga! Todo o esforço para chegar ao vice-capitão foi em vão.
I thought you were a human from this world, not a monster!
Achei que você fosse um humano deste mundo, não um monstro.
I'm unworthy of your praise.
Não mereço o seu elogio.
I just have more experience...
Só tenho mais experiência...
...in human-to-human combat.
lutando contra humanos.
Why are you gloating?
Por que está se gabando?
Daisuke, you're...
Daisuke, você está...
It's useless!
É inútil!
Not even death can stop them!
Nem mesmo a morte pode pará-los!
What?! What do you...?
O quê? Do que está...
Why? Why is nobody coming to help, after all this commotion?
Por que ninguém vem ajudar depois de todo esse barulho?
Just give up and die already, Captain Meld.
Desista e morra de uma vez, Capitão Meld.
No.
Não.
I'll take the coward's way out.
Prefiro a saída dos covardes.
What?! Hey!
O quê? Espere!
Paint the world in crimson...
Pinte o mundo de vermelho...
The matter with the king, the issue with the knights,
O problema com o rei e com os cavaleiros
everything they do is half-baked. They are mere humans, after all.
é que eles fazem tudo pela metade.
I suppose I must lend a hand.
Acho que devo interferir.
My god...
Meu Deus...
Yes. This is what Lord Ehit wishes.
Sim, esta é a vontade do Deus Ehit.
I guess I can't say, "I'm counting on you."
Acho que não posso dizer que conto com você.
That's your enemy.
Ela é sua inimiga.
Do your worst, knock them out!
Faça o seu pior. Acabe com eles!
Well, well. I suppose I should be impressed, Captain.
Ora, ora. Estou impressionada, capitão.
Quite clever. This could have been dangerous.
Que esperto. Isto podia ter sido perigoso.
What are you talking about?
Do que está falando?
Doesn't matter, how are you? You took quite a beating.
Não importa. Como você está? Apanhou bastante.
This is nothing.
Não foi nada.
And her?
E ela?
She's gone. Said we're half-baked.
Foi embora. Disse que somos incompetentes.
I see. In my defense, her intervention was part of my plan.
É mesmo?
It does seem like I have god's blessing.
Parece que tenho mesmo a bênção de Deus.
How mean can this god be?
Que maldade, não?
At any rate, we got rid of the biggest obstacle.
Seja como for, nos livramos do maior obstáculo.
Now all we need is to stay under Yaegashi's radar.
Agora só temos que ficar fora do radar da Yaegashi.
That's right. The king and the chancellor have lost their minds.
É verdade.
The Church was never an obstacle.
A Igreja nunca foi um obstáculo.
Yeah...
Não.
Now that the captain is out of the picture, nothing can stop us.
Com o capitão fora de cena, nada pode nos deter.
All right, let's speed this up.
Muito bem, vamos acelerar o passo.
Like a rolling stone, we keep tumbling towards...
Como uma pedra rolando, seguimos em direção...
The future that I desire...
ao futuro que desejo.
Can you show me the seashell that Myu gave you?
Posso ver a concha que a Myu te deu?
Sure, but...
Claro, mas...
What are you going to do with it?
O que fará com isso?
You'll see.
Você vai ver.
Are those people under attack?
Aquelas pessoas estão sendo atacadas?
Looks like bandits. Around 40 of them.
Parecem bandidos. Uns 40 deles.
Facing, I guess, 15 guards.
Contra, talvez, 15 guardas.
I'm impressed that they're holding their ground while being so outnumbered.
É impressionante que ainda consigam resistir.
Yes. That barrier isn't bad at all.
É. Aquela barreira é forte.
I see. They need to break that down to get through.
Entendi. Os bandidos precisam rompê-la para passar.
The bandits can't do anything if the guards shoot magic through the barrier.
Mas não podem fazer nada contra os guardas que lançam magia.
So why aren't the bandits retreating?
E por que não recuam?
Nobody native to this world would be able to maintain that huge barrier for long.
Nenhum nativo deste mundo poderia manter aquela barreira enorme por tanto tempo.
It might take a while, but the bandits just have to wait it out.
Pode levar um tempo, mas os bandidos só precisam esperar.
Hajime-kun, please! Help them! There could be--
Hajime, por favor, ajude-os! Deve ter...
Thank you, Hajime-kun!
Obrigada, Hajime!
If you see a criminal, step on the gas...
"Se vir um criminoso, pise fundo." É o que ensinam na autoescola, não é?
No way! Stop making up crazy rules!
Não é, não! Pare de inventar regras malucas!
What the...?!
Mas que...
If I'm going to do it, I'll show no mercy.
Se vou ajudar, não terei piedade.
I will kill every last one of them. You understand that, right, Kaori?
Matarei todos eles. Sabe disso, não sabe, Kaori?
Yes, I do.
Sim, sei.
Then go. I won't let them interfere.
— Então vá. Não vou deixá-los interferir. — Certo!
You stupid whore!
Vadia estúpida!
Kaori!
Kaori!
I knew it! It's you, Lily!
Eu sabia! É você, Lily!
I thought I recognized that barrier.
Bem que reconheci aquela barreira.
I had no idea why you would be out here, so I wasn't sure.
Mas não sabia o que você estaria fazendo aqui fora, então não tinha certeza.
It seems like lady luck hasn't abandoned me yet.
Parece que a Senhora Sorte ainda não me abandonou.
Kaori, are you done healing?
Kaori, já curou todo mundo?
You're Nagumo-san, aren't you? Long time no see.
Você é o Nagumo, não é? Há quanto tempo!
Shizuku and the others told me about your survival.
Me contaram que você tinha sobrevivido.
I'm so glad you're safe...
Que bom que está bem.
Kaori was in shambles the whole time you were gone.
A Kaori ficou arrasada durante a sua ausência.
Come on! This is not the time for that!
Pare! Não é hora para isso!
I also heard about Kaori's once-in-a-lifetime romantic pledge.
Eu também soube da jura de amor dela.
Please do fill me in on the details later.
Por favor, conte-me os detalhes depois.
But anyway, who are you?
Mas quem é você, afinal?
Huh?
Como?
Hajime-kun!
Hajime!
She's the princess! The princess!
Ela é a princesa!
Princess Liliana of the Kingdom of Heiligh!
A Princesa Liliana, do Reino Heiligh!
Don't you remember?!
Não se lembra?
Huh? Oh, right.
O quê? Entendi...
I didn't know getting forgotten could hurt so much...
Não sabia que ser esquecida doía tanto...
Lily, don't cry! Hajime-kun is the weird one here!
Lily, não chore! O Hajime é anormal!
A normal person would never forget you, Lily!
Uma pessoa normal não se esqueceria de você!
Hey, am I being verbally abused right now?
Ei, isso é abuso verbal.
So, what is the princess doing out here?
Mas o que a princesa está fazendo aqui?
Lily...?
Lily...
Aiko-san was... kidnapped.
A Aiko foi... sequestrada.
For a while now, I've felt that something was wrong with the people at the castle.
Há algum tempo, eu sentia que havia algo errado com as pessoas no castelo.
Father's support of the Holy Church was growing more radical each day,
O apoio do meu pai à Igreja Sagrada ficava mais radical a cada dia.
and his worship of Lord Ehit was nothing short of feverish.
Seu fervor por Ehit só crescia.
At first, I just thought he was just trying to deepen his bond with the Church.
No começo, achei que ele só quisesse estreitar os laços dele com a Igreja.
But I still couldn't help but feel that something was wrong.
Mas eu sabia que havia algo errado.
It was then that knights and soldiers began to appear lethargic,
Então os soldados e cavaleiros começaram a ficar letárgicos,
as if suffering from some disease.
como se estivessem doentes.
The branding of Nagumo-san as a heretic was also suspicious.
Marcar o Nagumo como herege também foi suspeito.
Your efforts at the town of Ur and the Great Orcus Labyrinth were ignored,
Seus esforços em Ur e no Labirinto de Orcus foram ignorados,
as well as Aiko-san's objection and arguments.
assim como o protesto e os argumentos da Aiko.
Of course, I objected to my father as well.
Eu também me posicionei contra meu pai,
But he was determined to brand Nagumo-san the enemy of god, no matter what.
mas ele estava decidido a considerar o Nagumo um inimigo de Deus.
Father began to look at me as if he was looking at an enemy.
Meu pai passou a me olhar como se eu fosse um inimigo.
I grew afraid, so I went to Aiko-san to discuss the matter.
Fiquei com medo e procurei a Aiko para falar sobre isso.
But Aiko-san was kidnapped by a nun from the Divine Mountain.
Mas ela foi sequestrada por uma freira e levada à Montanha Divina.
I thought that the nun was the mastermind behind this
Imaginei que a freira estivesse por trás de tudo.
I had to tell someone. But it's natural to assume that the castle is being watched.
Eu tinha que contar isso a alguém, mas o castelo estava sendo vigiado.
So I had to find someone who could help.
Eu precisava achar ajuda.
The first people I thought of were you two, Kaori and Nagumo-san.
Kaori, você e o Nagumo foram as primeiras pessoas em que pensei.
Shizuku told me that you had travelled west.
A Shizuku disse que vocês tinham ido para o oeste.
The rest you already know.
O resto vocês já sabem.
I thought I would start by asking Duke Zengen for help,
Decidi começar pedindo ajuda ao Duque Zengen,
so I asked a caravan to let me ride along.
então peguei carona em uma caravana.
I never thought I'd run into you along the way.
Jamais pensei que encontraria vocês no caminho.
A while ago, I would have said that this was god's blessing.
Antigamente, eu teria dito que isso era uma bênção de Deus.
But right now, I am afraid of the Church...
Mas, agora, tenho medo da igreja.
What is going on?
O que está acontecendo?
Lily...
Lily...
I suppose, for starters, I have to go save our teacher.
Antes de tudo, terei que salvar nossa professora.
Would you do that?!
Você faria isso?
Don't get the wrong idea, it's not for the kingdom.
Não entenda mal. Não farei isso pelo reino.
I'm doing this for her.
Farei isso por ela.
For Aiko-san...
Pela Aiko...
I'm the reason she got kidnapped. I can't just leave her to suffer.
Ela foi sequestrada por minha causa. Não posso deixar que ela sofra.
That said, if the cause of all of this got in the way of my rescue operation,
Então, se os culpados por tudo isso atrapalharem minha missão de resgate,
I'd have no choice but to beat them up, whomever it turned out to be.
terei que surrá-los, quem quer que sejam.
Then all I can do is hope that's what'll happen.
Então vou torcer para que isso aconteça.
Thank you, Nagumo-san.
Obrigada, Nagumo.
The Divine Mountain that she was taken to is one of the Great Labyrinths.
A Montanha Divina, onde ela está, é um dos grandes labirintos.
I wonder what kind of God's Age magic I can get there?
Que tipo de magia encontrarei lá?
Hajime, you're so awesome.
Hajime, você é sensacional.
Hajime-san is making that face again.
O Hajime está fazendo aquela cara de novo.
It makes my heart throb!
Faz meu coração pular!
Hmm. Master, having such a vicious look on your face...
Mestre, esse seu olhar perverso
It makes me wet!
me deixa toda molhada!
What are my students trying to do...? What could it be?
O que meus alunos estão tentando fazer?
Eliminating the "Irregular"... Irregular? Irregular...
Eliminar o "Irregular"...
Nagumo-kun.
Nagumo.
Yeah, what is it, Sensei?
Sim. O que foi, professora?
What?!
O quê?
Over here.
Aqui.
Nagumo-kun, is that you?! What?!
Nagumo, é você?
This is the top floor; this is the Divine Mountain, what?!
Estamos no último andar!
Yeah, so, um, calm down, Sensei.
É, bem... Acalme-se, professora.
I'm almost done checking for traps.
Estou terminando de procurar por armadilhas.
Why are you so surprised? You noticed that I was coming, right?
Por que está tão surpresa? Percebeu que eu estava vindo, não é?
Even though I thought I had completely masked my presence...
Achei que eu tivesse mascarado a minha presença...
Noticed? What? Huh?
Percebi? Como assim?
Well, you did call out my name. You must have detected me.
Bem, você chamou o meu nome. Deve ter me detectado.
What?! Well, anyway, why are you here?
O quê? Bem, de qualquer forma, o que faz aqui?
To rescue you, of course.
Estou resgatando você.
--Y-You came here for me? - Nagumo-kun? For me?
Veio até aqui por mim, Nagumo?
--She's not already brainwashed or something, is she? --Y-You came here for me? Nagumo-kun? For me?
— Isso não é alguma lavagem cerebral, é? — Só por mim?
What? No! You can't! So sudden! I'm your teacher...
O quê? Não! Você não pode! Sou sua professora.
I'm just trying to take this off.
Só quero remover isto.
Having your magic power sealed away is bad, right?
Ter seu poder mágico selado é ruim.
Or is there a reason you need to keep this?
Há alguma razão para ficar com isto?
Oh, right, I see...
Certo, entendi...
What did you think I was...?
O que achou que eu estava...
I'm sorry, it's nothing...
Nada, não... Me desculpe.
How did you know I was being held here? Nobody else knew...
Como sabia que eu estava presa aqui?
The princess told me.
A princesa me contou.
The princess? Princess Liliana?
A Princesa Liliana?
She saw you get kidnapped.
Ela viu quando sequestraram você.
She figured the entire castle was under surveillance,
Imaginou que o castelo todo estivesse sob vigilância,
so she couldn't tell Amanogawa and the others.
então não podia contar ao Amanogawa e aos outros.
She decided to leave the capital all alone.
Saiu da capital sozinha...
To find help.
para buscar ajuda.
Liliana-san did that? And Nagumo-kun, you responded.
A Liliana fez isso?
Yeah. It does seem like I'm at least partly responsible for this situation.
Atendi. Sinto que ao menos parte disso foi culpa minha.
I'm sure I'm the last person you wanted to see, but...
Sou a última pessoa que você queria ver,
Well, I hope you'll put up with me until the others join.
mas espero que me ature até que os outros cheguem.
You're definitely not the last person I wanted to see.
Você definitivamente não é a última pessoa que eu queria ver.
It's true, I haven't completely gotten over what happened with Shimizu-kun.
Admito que ainda não superei totalmente o que houve com o Shimizu.
I might never get over that.
Talvez nunca supere.
But still, I think I understand what you felt when you pulled that trigger.
Mas, ainda assim, acho que entendo o que você sentiu quando puxou o gatilho.
Sensei...
Professora...
I wasn't able to say this properly back then, so let me say it now.
Não pude dizer naquele dia, mas permita-me dizer agora:
Thank you for saving me.
obrigada por me salvar.
I'm sorry I made you pull that trigger.
Sinto muito por ter feito você puxar o gatilho.
I'm just doing what I want.
Só estou fazendo o que quero.
I accept your gratitude but reject your apology.
Aceito sua gratidão, mas rejeito as desculpas.
Anyway, let's get going.
Precisamos sair logo daqui.
Nagumo-kun, please be careful.
Nagumo, por favor, tenha cuidado.
The Church adamantly branded you a heretic.
A Igreja o marcou como herege.
Also, the person who kidnapped me might be--
Além disso, talvez a pessoa que me sequestrou seja...
I know. Whatever the case may be, once I get you back to safety,
Eu sei. Seja como for, quando você estiver em segurança,
I have to take care of my own business here,
tenho meus próprios assuntos para tratar aqui.
and in order to do that, I probably need to take on the Church anyway.
Para isso, terei que enfrentar a Igreja.
I see, so you're ready for this.
Entendi. Então está preparado para isso.
I am.
Estou.
Dammit, what is this timing...
Droga! Logo agora?
Or rather, this might actually work out in our favor.
Não, isso pode ser vantajoso para nós.
Did something happen?
Aconteceu alguma coisa?
The Demons are attacking.
Os demônios estão atacando.
What we just heard was the barrier surrounding the capital being shattered.
Destruíram a barreira em volta da capital.
The Demons are attacking?!
Os demônios estão atacando?
Yes, the Heiligh Kingdom is being invaded.
Estão. O Reino Heiligh está sendo invadido.
It can't be...
Não pode ser...
Taken completely by surprise.
Foi pego de surpresa.
Th-That's terrible...
Isso é terrível!
Sensei, regroup with Amanogawa and the others first. We'll talk more later.
Professora, encontre o Amanogawa e os outros. Conversaremos depois.
Y-Yes.
Está bem.
Disintegration...?
Desintegração?
Precisely.
Exatamente.
Irregular, my name is Noint.
Irregular, eu me chamo Noint.
As god's apostle, I will remove the unneeded pieces from the god's board.
Como Apóstola de Deus, removerei as peças desnecessárias do tabuleiro dele.
Next episode, "Invasion of the Capital."
A seguir: "Invasão da Capital".